SARA SOLTANIFAR



soltanifar.sara@yahoo.com



(647)561 0000



LINKEDIN URL

https://www.linkedin.com/in/s ara-soltanifar-a581bb1b7/

OBJECTIVE

I'm Sara Soltanifar, a Graphic Designer with a Master's in Art History from Iran. I've worked as a Graphic Designer and Painter and am currently studying Interactive Media Design at Seneca College. I love building strong connections and am dedicated to quality and process improvement. Known for my energy, positive attitude, and commitment to fostering business growth through great relationships.

EXPERIENCE

Customer Service Jun 2022 - present

Lacoste store, Vaughn mills

Instructor Aug 2018 - Nov 2020

Painting Instructor, Iran

Graphic Design Jul 2018 - Sep 2020

Sanmar Architecture and Design Studio, Iran

Graphic Design Jan2019 - Sep2020

Freelance, Mehrdad Mall, Iran

Graphic Designer Feb 2016 - Jun 2018

Sazeh Gostaran Architecture Company, Iran

Junior graphic designer Oct 2013 - Mar 2016

Payesh Company, Iran

EDUCATION

Interactive Media Design May2024

Seneca Collage, York University

Art Fundamental Jan 2024

Seneca Collage, York University

General Arts – English for Academic Purposes (GEA) May2023-Dec2023

Seneca Collage, Newnham Campus

Master's Degree in Art History Dec 2019

Islamic Azad University Science and Research Tehran Branch. Iran

Bachelor's Degree in Drama, Stage Design Mar 2012

Islamic Azad University Central Tehran Branch. Iran

SKILLS

Advanced skills using Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Word Press and Adobe Photoshop, Audition, Illustrator, InDesign, XD, Figma, Motion Graphic and Editing. Strong understanding of design Principles, Typography, and Color Theory.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE OR LEADERSHIP

Customer Service July 2020

Thriding Studio Gallery, Markham

Event staff Oct 2019

Art Toronto, Toronto